<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
	<partie nom="Home" href="/">
		<contenu><![CDATA[<span class="punch">NinjaTooken is a free FPS online solo and multiplayer game in a medieval japanese universe.</span>
		<h3>Evolutionary, free, multiplayer, online.</h3>
		<a href="/inscription.php" alt="Which ninja are you ?" title="Which ninja are you ?" class="pastille">Which ninja<br/>are you ?</a>
		<p>Ninja Tooken transports you into a universe where ninjas are merciless. The game’s purpose? Kill them ALL !!<br/><br/>
		To begin, create your account. Then, choose your ninja class: Katon (the fire), Suiton (the water), Futon (the wind), Doton (the earth), Raiton (the lightning).<br/>
		Then, the principle is simple: the more you kill, the more you’ll gain experience.<br/>
		These points will allow you to develop your ninja according to your class.<br/><br/>
		But be careful: every element has his worst enemy. For example, if you belong to Katon, distrust especially Suitons.<br/>
		With an integrated chat and till 14 ninjas in each map, every game is different but always insanely amazing! So come to fight, do your best in the game, and participate to the development of Ninja Tooken.<br/><br/>
		And NinjaTooken that's also ##NUM_JOUEURS## players who win ##NUM_EXPERIENCE## points of expériences : join the community !</p>

		<h3>The "NinjaTooken"</h3>
		<div class="box gold nt gradient">
			<span class="number"></span>
			<span class="login">-Delton-</span>
			<span class="description">winner the <a href="/message.php?ID=272352">12 of may, 2013</a>, and the <a href="/message.php?ID=290784">18 of august, 2013</a></span>
		</div>
		<p>The ancients NinjaTooken :</p>
		<div class="box grey nto gradient">
			<span class="number"></span>
			<span class="login" style="width:215px">Pein-rikoudu, Horoshimaru and Suikeii</span>
			<span class="description">winners the <a href="/message.php?ID=245781">10 of february, 2013</a></span>
		</div>
		<div class="box grey nto gradient">
			<span class="number"></span>
			<span class="login">Rw_light</span>
			<span class="description">winner the <a href="/message.php?ID=235008">22 of december, 2012</a></span>
		</div>
		<div class="box grey nto gradient">
			<span class="number"></span>
			<span class="login">Pein-Rikoudu</span>
			<span class="description">winner the <a href="/message.php?ID=217944">20 of october, 2012</a></span>
		</div>
		<div class="box grey nto gradient">
			<span class="number"></span>
			<span class="login" style="width:210px">kether, Blade-Inferno and Strikesword</span>
			<span class="description">winners the <a href="/message.php?ID=182447">8 of july, 2012</a></span>
		</div>
		<div class="box grey nto gradient">
			<span class="number"></span>
			<span class="login">Fusako.Uchiha</span>
			<span class="description">winner the <a href="/message.php?ID=165196">21 of may, 2012</a></span>
		</div>
		<div class="box grey nto gradient">
			<span class="number"></span>
			<span class="login">Ninjamza</span>
			<span class="description">winner the <a href="/message.php?ID=160075">21 of april, 2012</a></span>
		</div>
		<div class="box grey nto gradient">
			<span class="number"></span>
			<span class="login">Kether</span>
			<span class="description">winner the <a href="/message.php?ID=142474">25 of february, 2012</a></span>
		</div>
		<div class="box grey nto gradient">
			<span class="number"></span>
			<span class="login">L-orbe-shuriken</span>
			<span class="description">winner the <a href="/message.php?ID=119260">13 of november, 2011</a></span>
		</div>
		<div class="box grey nto gradient">
			<span class="number"></span>
			<span class="login">Yoyosam</span>
			<span class="description">winner the <a href="/message.php?ID=109224">22 of october, 2011</a></span>
		</div>
		<div class="box grey nto gradient">
			<span class="number"></span>
			<span class="login">Rydax</span>
			<span class="description">winner the <a href="/message.php?ID=72948#message72948">16 of july, 2011</a>, <a href="/message.php?ID=79127">13 of august, 2011</a>, and <a href="/message.php?ID=93504">18 of september, 2011</a></span>
		</div>
		<div class="box grey nto gradient">
			<span class="number"></span>
			<span class="login">Gaara76</span>
			<span class="description">winner the <a href="/message.php?ID=68359#message68359">26 of june, 2011</a></span>
		</div>
		<div class="box grey nto gradient">
			<span class="number"></span>
			<span class="login">Mistral</span>
			<span class="description">winner the <a href="/message.php?ID=60173#message60173">14 of may, 2011</a>, <a href="/message.php?ID=63228#message63228">29 of may, 2011</a>, and <a href="/message.php?ID=64492#message64492">5 of june, 2011</a></span>
		</div>
		<div class="box grey nto gradient">
			<span class="number"></span>
			<span class="login">Zanhkraft</span>
			<span class="description">winner the <a href="/message.php?ID=33451#message33451">13th/14th of November, 2010</a></span>
		</div>


		<h3>Ranking</h3>
		<div id="classementSelect">
			<a href="#" id="Experience" class="colonne on" title="Experience">Experience</a>
			<a href="#" id="Assassinnat" class="colonne" title="Murder">Murdering</a>
			<a href="#" id="Course" class="colonne" title="Race">Race</a>
			<span href="#" class="colonne" title="class" id="Classe">Class : <span id="type">All</span>
				<span class="classe">
					<a href="#" title="" class="on">All</a>]]></contenu>

		<contenu><![CDATA[</span>
			</span>
		</div>
		<ul id="classement"></ul>
		<br class="clear"/><br/>
		<a href="#" id="classementNext">More ninjas !</a>
		<h3>Class distribution</h3>]]></contenu>

		<contenu><![CDATA[<br/><br/>Last update ##DATE##<br/><br/>]]></contenu>

		<contenu><![CDATA[<a href="/chat/?channelID=1&lang=en" onclick="javascript:pop('/chat/?channelID=1&lang=en',1000,650);return false;" target="_blank" rel="nofollow" class="chat"><span>Open NT's Chatroom</span></a><br/>
		<div id="lastSide">
			<ul class="onglet">
				<li><a href="#" id="new" title="Last news">News</a></li>
				<li><a href="#" id="message" title="Last messages">Message</a></li>
				<li><a href="#" id="sujet" title="Last subjects">Subject</a></li>
				<li><a href="#" id="clan" title="Last clans">Clan</a></li>
			</ul>
			<div class="lastContain"></div>
		</div>
		<iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/plugins/likebox.php?locale=en_US&amp;href=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Fpages%2FNinja-Tooken%2F102601529783806&amp;width=237&amp;colorscheme=dark&amp;show_faces=true&amp;stream=false&amp;header=false&amp;height=258" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" style="border:none; overflow:hidden; width:237px; height:258px;" allowTransparency="true"></iframe>
		<h3>Partners</h3>]]></contenu>

	</partie>
	<partie nom="Community">
		<partie nom="Forum" href=""/>
		<partie nom="Clan" href="/clan-ninja.php"/>
		<partie nom="Abuse Moderation" href="/abuse.php"/>
		<partie nom="Rules" href="/reglement.php"/>
	</partie>
	<partie nom="PLAY" href="/jouer.php"/>
	<partie nom="Ninja's handbook" href="/manuel-ninja/game-control.php">
		<partie nom="Beginners Guide">
			<partie nom="Game control" href="/manuel-ninja/game-control.php">
				<contenu><![CDATA[<img src="/img/ninjatooken1.jpg" class="right" alt=""/>
				Nothing’s easier than playing Ninja Tooken !!<br/><br/>
				Like most of FPS, you have to use the"W, A, S, D" keys to move.<br/><br/>
				You can also use Spacebar to jump (or right-click), "1, 2, 3, 4, 5" for weapons and "Q, E, R, F, T" for jutsus... But you can also change your weapons or jutsus by rolling the scroll wheel up and down. It's very usefull, because they are all (what a coincidence!) grouped together...<br/><br/>
				Of course if you don't like this arrangement, you can customize it in <a href="/manuel-ninja/parametrage-touche.php" title="game options">game options</a>.<br/><br/>
				Icing on the cake: you can also change mouse sensitivity in game options. Damn good, right ?<br/><br/>]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="Play Solo" href="/manuel-ninja/play-solo.php">
				<contenu><![CDATA[Two types of mission are available in the Ninja Tooken "Single Game" : Race and Murdering.<br/>
				Complete these missions will allow you to improve the control of your ninja during moves and attacks, while makin' EXP !<br/>
				To complete these missions, launch a single game, then press the "chat key" ("Enter" by default) , when you’re near the corresponding icons.
				<br/><br/>
				<h3>Race</h3>
				<img src="/img/course.jpg" alt="Race" class="right"/>
				To complete these missions, you'll have to collect golden coins in a short time.<br/>
				You succeed the mission by collecting all the coins before the time is elapsed, earning EXP (depending on the mission’s number of coins and time). On the other hand, if you don't manage to collect all the coins before the deadline, you loose the mission and don't earn any EXP point.<br/>
				Don't worry! You can relaunch each mission as many time as you want !<br/>
				<br/>
				<h3>Murdering</h3>
				<img src="/img/assassinat.jpg" alt="Murdering" class="left"/>
				A ninja’s head is on contract! To achieve it, you will have to assassinate him on the map. If your target or another ninja kills you, the mission fails. If you exceed the time limitation, the mission fails.<br/>
				You already understood that you’ll have to show a true ninja instinct to complete this mission.<br/>
				Don’t worry! You can relaunch each mission as many time as you want !<br/>
				<br/><br/><br/><br/>
				For each one of these missions (Race and Murdering), you’ll be helped by an indicator, which allows you to know the location of the nearest coin or the ninja to murder. In the up left corner, you’ll see a window containing updates about the mission type, the time left, and specific informations for each mission.]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="Network Game" href="/manuel-ninja/network-game.php">
				<contenu><![CDATA[<img src="/img/reseau.jpg" alt="parties réseaux" class="right"/>
				Four types of games are available at the creation of a network game :<br/>
				<br/>
				<h3>Standard game</h3>
				No time, no team, no flag: just Fight !<br/>
				Every connected player will have to fight for his survival with his own means, without help (comrades) and without time limit.<br/>
				<br/>
				<h3>Team game</h3>
				For this game, two teams are engaged in a merciless war! Every new player who connects joins the least numerous team.<br/>
				The enemies are in red, the allies in blue, and it’s not possible to kill an ally.<br/>
				<br/>
				<h3>Timed game</h3>
				You have 10 minutes to make the game yours. Then, the countdown is reset and a new round begins! No team, just enemies !<br/>
				<br/>
				<h3>Scroll mode</h3>
				A scroll appears on the map. Catch it to win several bonuses, then run for the indicated area where you will be regenerating and where damages are divided by two! If you manage to stay in the area for 45 secondes in a row, you win the game, thus earning many experience points!]]></contenu>
			</partie>
		</partie>
		<partie nom="My Ninja">
			<partie nom="General Description" href="/manuel-ninja/general-description.php">
				<contenu><![CDATA[<p align="center"><img src="/img/fresque.jpg" class="center" alt=""/><br/></p>
				Ninja Tooken transports you in a Japanese based universe where ninjas are merciless. The game's purpose? Kill them all !<br/><br/>
				To begin, <a href="/inscription.php">create your account</a>. Then, choose your ninja class: Katon (the fire), Suiton (the water), Futon (the wind), Doton (the earth), Raiton (the lightning).<br/>
				Then, the principle is simple: the more you kill, the more you’ll gain experience.<br/>
				These points will allow you to develop your ninja according to your class.<br/><br/>
				But be careful: every element has his worst enemy. For example, if you belong to Katon, distrust especially Suitons.]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="Life and Chakra" href="/manuel-ninja/life-chakra.php">
				<contenu><![CDATA[<img src="/img/infosPerso.jpg" alt="interface" class="right"/>
				The life and the chakra are two very important elements for your ninja: if you don’t have any life points left, you’ll die. And if you have no more chakra points available, you can’t use jutsus anymore.<br/>
				These two capacities can be increased with the points you gain at each level, meaning how many you put into it.<br/>
				You can also recover the life or chakra lost during a battle, with the bonuses spread onto the map. The bonus " bowl of ramen " gives some life, and the bonus "Ying Yang" gives some chakra.<br/>
				Besides, the chakra regenerates itself at a rate of 5 points per second.]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="Experience" href="/manuel-ninja/experience.php">
				<contenu><![CDATA[<img src="/img/experience.jpg" alt="un niveau en plus" class="right"/>
				The experience can be gained by several means.<br/>
				In <a href="/manuel-ninja/partie-solo.php" title="Play solo">Play Solo</a>, you gain some experience when you kill a ninja, but you can also gain it by succeeding the available missions.<br/>
				In the Network mode, the experience results only from the ninjas you kill. The higher the ninja’s level you’ve just knock down is, the more EXP you’ll get.<br/>
				Then you must necessarily take risks, and challenge the best ninjas.<br/>
				Once gained, this experience allows you to level up, and each level gives points of capacities and jutsus.<br/>
				<br/>
				You will find in the <a href="/manuel-ninja/partie-solo.php" title="beginners' guide">"beginners' guide"</a> all the information concerning the various manners to get some experience in Ninja Tooken !<br/>
				<br/>
				<h3>Ranks</h3>
				<br/>
				The rank of your ninja depends directly on its level, and thus on the gained experience :<br/>
				<table border="0">
					<tr>
						<td width="100"><strong>Niveau 1-9</strong></td>
						<td>Cockroach</td>
					</tr>
					<tr>
						<td><strong>Niveau 10-19</strong></td>
						<td>Student</td>
					</tr>
					<tr>
						<td><strong>Niveau 20-49</strong></td>
						<td>Genin</td>
					</tr>
					<tr>
						<td><strong>Niveau 50-69</strong></td>
						<td>Chunin</td>
					</tr>
					<tr>
						<td><strong>Niveau 70-89</strong></td>
						<td>Jōnin</td>
					</tr>
					<tr>
						<td><strong>Niveau 90-100</strong></td>
						<td>Sannin</td>
					</tr>
				</table>
				<br/><br/>
				If you read me, you’re most certainly a cockroach! But do not worry, this step quickly ends, and you’ll soon get to use the most powerful jutsus.]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="Capacities" href="/manuel-ninja/capacitie.php">
				<contenu><![CDATA[The capacities are the base of your ninja. At each level up, you will gain three points to distribute according to your will and the way you want to develop your ninja. You want him to be stronger? faster? more tenacious? It's up to you !<br/><br/>
				<h3>4 capacities and their various effects<br/></h3>
				<img src="/img/skecthfuton.jpg" class="right" alt=""/>
				<h4>Strength</h4>
				The Strength acts on two aspects of your ninja: the stronger you are, the more powerful your weapons will be (but only weapons and not jutsus!).<br/>
				But this capacity does not only improve the damages, it also allows your ninja to throw kunais, shurikens, and other weapons farther.<br/>
				<br/>
				<h4>Speed</h4>
				The Speed allows your ninja to run faster. Do not forget that a good ninja is furtive and sneaky, with a fast attack and retreat.<br/>
				<br/>
				<h4>Life</h4>
				The life's gauge is directly proportional to the Life. By putting points into it, you will increase your maximum health points.<br/>
				<br/>
				<h4>Chakra</h4>
				The Chakra is working like the Life. The more you put in it, the bigger your chakra gauge will be.]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="Jutsus" href="/manuel-ninja/jutsu.php">
				<contenu><![CDATA[With jutsus, we're getting down to business !<br/>
				A point will be given to you for every level up. You can place it into the jutsu you wish to develop, or in the one that you want to learn.<br/>
				Unlike the capacities, you won’t have all the jutsus at the beginning of your adventure. They are only available according to your progresses and class. But do not worry, every jutsu point is removable at any time, allowing you to develop another ability.<br/>
				<br/>
				<h3>Types of jutsus</h3>
				Jutsus divides up into several categories. There are passive or active (manually activated) jutsus. There are attack and defense jutsus, and even movement ones. You can really specialize your ninja as you wish, and improve your strategy at its best.<br/>
				<br/>
				<h3>Generals Jutsus</h3>
				Most of the jutsus are common to the five classes (Katon, Futon, Raiton, Doton, Suiton), the others are specific to certain classes. We shall see them later. Let's see now these general jutsus.<br/>
				<br/>
				<h4>Chakra Ball</h4>
				<img src="/img/jutsus/boule.png" alt="Chakra Ball" class="left"/>
				This distance attack is very simple, it allows you to throw a ball of chakra. This ball is not affected by the gravity, and thus can be sent from long distance while remaining very precise.<br/>
				Improvement according to the jutsu points affected: bigger, more powerful, but increased chakra consumption.<br/>
				<br/>
				<h4>Double Jump</h4>
				<img src="/img/jutsus/saut.png" alt="Double Jump" class="left"/>
				As its name indicates it, the double jump allows you to make a second jump following the first one (while in the air) to reach high zones. The double jump is a passive jutsu, it isn’t necessary to activate it; it doesn’t require any chakra.<br/>
				Improvement according to the jutsu points affected: higher jumps.<br/>
				<br/>
				<h4>Shield</h4>
				<img src="/img/jutsus/bouclier.png" alt="Shield" class="left"/>
				The shield allows you to reduce damage undergone. But this jutsus isn’t passive, it’s necessary to activate it, and it’s active only for a while.<br/>
				Improvement according to the jutsu points affected: lasts longer, higher damage reduction but increased chakra consumption.<br/>
				<br/>
				<h4>Walk on walls</h4>
				<img src="/img/jutsus/mur.png" alt="Walk on walls" class="left"/>
				This active jutsu allows you to walk on very steep slopes and vertical surfaces during a certain laps of time. By default, it is activated by pressing the « Ctrl » key. It consumes chakra at each release, but don’t worry, this very useful jutsu is economic.<br/>
				Improvement according to the jutsu points affected: lasts longer but increased chakra consumption.<br/>
				<br/>
				<h4>Explosion</h4>
				<img src="/img/jutsus/deflagration.png" alt="Explosion" class="left"/>
				The explosion is the most powerful common jutsu. To call the elemental forces, a short incantation time is necessary, allowing your targets to escape the effect area. If it’s not the case, they will be caught in a sphere of chakra coming from your ninja. It’s highly inadvisable to stay in the effect area of an explosion! If you plan to use it, you must foresee a good dose of chakra because if the explosion is very powerful, it also consumes a high amount of chakra.<br/>
				Improvement according to the jutsu points affected: higher damages and diameter, but increased chakra consumption.<br/>
				<br/><br/>
				Let's see now the specific jutsus for every class...<br/>
				<br/>
				<h3 id="classe">Jutsus by classes</h3>
				Each of the <a href="/manuel-ninja/classe.php">five classes</a> have two special jutsus<br/>
				<br/>
				<h4>Katon, the fire</h4>
				<ul>
					<li>
						<h4>Protection against the fire</h4>
						<img src="/img/jutsus/resistance.png" alt="Protection against the fire" class="left"/>
						This protection decreases the damages of Chakra Ball, Explosion, Phoenix, and explosives (barrel, or explosive kunais). This passive jutsu doesn’t consume chakra.<br/>
						Improvement according to the jutsu points affected: increased protection.
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>Phoenix</h4>
						<img src="/img/jutsus/phoenix.png" alt="phoenix" class="left"/>
						This attack allows your ninja to send the spirit of fire in front of him. Once the spirit hits the ground, an enormous explosion occurs, seriously burning the enemies taken in the elemental fury.<br/>
						Improvement according to the jutsu points affected: bigger effect area and higher damages and range, but increased chakra consumption.<br/>
						<strong>To use this jutsu, your ninja must be going berserk. It occurs when you’ve lost 50 % of your maximum health points !</strong>
					</li>
				</ul>
				<h4>Suiton, the water</h4>
				<ul>
					<li>
						<h4>Walk on water</h4>
						<img src="/img/jutsus/marcher.png" alt="Walk on water" class="left"/>
						This jutsu simply allows you to walk on water. Unlike « walk on walls », it does not consume chakra.<br/>
						Improvement according to the jutsu points affected: lasts longer.
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>Tsunami</h4>
						<img src="/img/jutsus/vague.png" alt="Tsunami" class="left"/>
						Call upon the devastating power of the aqueous spirits from a zone on the ground. Once invocated, the wave follows the ground on a linear trajectory and deals important damages to all the wet enemies.<br/>
						Improvement according to the jutsu points affected: bigger effect area and higher damages and range, but increased chakra consumption.<br/>
						<strong>To use this jutsu, your ninja must be going berserk. It occurs when you’ve lost 50 % of your maximum health points !</strong>
					</li>
				</ul>
				<h4>Futon, the wind</h4>
				<ul>
					<li>
						<h4>Invisibility</h4>
						<img src="/img/jutsus/transparence.png" alt="Invisibility" class="left"/>
						The transparency is passive, and does not consume a chakra, while being permanent ! No need to activate it, you will have this advantage all the time.<br/>
						Improvement according to the jutsu points affected: higher transparency.
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>Tornado</h4>
						<img src="/img/jutsus/tornade.png" alt="Tornado" class="left"/>
						Release the power of the wind during a limited moment. From your ninja to the targeted zone, the tornado moves in spiral and deals big damages to all the enemies nearby.<br/>
						Improvement according to the jutsu points affected: bigger effect area and higher damages and range, but increased chakra consumption and invocation time.<br/>
						<strong>To use this jutsu, your ninja must be going berserk. It occurs when you’ve lost 50 % of your maximum health points !</strong>
					</li>
				</ul>
				<h4>Doton, the earth</h4>
				<ul>
					<li>
						<h4>Metamorphosis</h4>
						<img src="/img/jutsus/rock.png" alt="Metamorphosis" class="left"/>
						This doton jutsu allows your ninja to mutate temporarily into a rock. To hide and perform a sneaky attack, there’s nothing better! The metamorphosis is an active jutsu, which nullifies as soon as you move.<br/>
						Improvement according to the points of chakra: longer transformation time.
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>Thorns of rock</h4>
						<img src="/img/jutsus/pieux.png" alt="Thorns of rock" class="left"/>
						Call upon the power of the earth from a zone. Once called, thorns appear from the earth and come to impale the enemies dealing them important damages.<br/>
						Improvement according to the jutsu points affected: higher damages, range and thorns number, but increased chakra consumption.<br/>
						<strong>To use this jutsu, your ninja must be going berserk. It occurs when you’ve lost 50 % of your maximum health points !</strong>
					</li>
				</ul>
				<h4>Raiton, the lightning</h4>
				<ul>
					<li>
						<h4>Rain of steel</h4>
						<img src="/img/jutsus/multi.png" alt="Rain of steel" class="left"/>
						The multishot is a passive jutsu allowing you to increase your ninja’s fire rate. It works for all <a href="/manuel-ninja/weapon.php" title="physical attacks">physical attacks</a>.<br/>
						Improvement according to the jutsu points affected: increased fire rate (the time between 2 attacks is limited to 150ms).
					</li>
					<li>
						<h4>Teleportation</h4>
						<img src="/img/jutsus/teleportation.png" alt="Teleportation" class="left"/>
						Call the powers of thunder on a zone. Once called, the lightning transports the ninja towards this area with a surprising speed in exchange for a few health points.<br/>
						Improvement according to the jutsu points affected: higher teleportation distance, but also higher health points required.
					</li>
				</ul>]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="Weapons" href="/manuel-ninja/weapon.php">
				<contenu><![CDATA[<img src="/img/ninjamec.jpg" class="right" alt=""/>
				Weapons in Ninja Tooken are as important as jutsus, do not forget them !<br/>
				<br/>
				The damages dealt by weapons is obviously depending on the type of weapon, but also on the <a href="/manuel-ninja/aptitude.php" title="Capacities">strength</a> of your ninja.<br/>
				<br/>
				<br/>
				Let's detail now each weapon :<br/>
				<br style="clear:both"/>
				<h4>Katana</h4>
				<img src="/img/armes/katana.png" alt="katana" class="left"/>
				The katana is the unique hand-to-hand fight weapon. Being more difficult to use in the ninjas’ distant fights, it deals very important damages! If you have the opportunity to get closer to another ninja, a blow of katana in the spine will be the ideal to finish him/her in no time !<br/>
				<br/>
				<h4>Kunaï</h4>
				<img src="/img/armes/kunai.png" alt="kunaï" class="left"/>
				The kunai is one of the basic ninja weapons. You have a good package of it, so use them! If you don’t have any left, you can always gather new ones in the weapon boxes spread onto every map. The kunai is not thrown straight because of the gravity getting involved... In order to improve the kunai trajectoty and reach farther targets, it is necessary that you increase your ninja’s Strength.<br/>
				<br/>
				<h4>Explosive Kunaï </h4>
				<img src="/img/armes/explo.png" alt="Explosive Kunaï " class="left"/>
				The explosive kunai is used in the same way as the standard kunai, but it explodes at the end of a rather short time, or in contact with the target. Do not stay nearby! You can pick up more explosive kunai in the specific boxes.<br/>
				<br/>
				<h4>Shuriken</h4>
				<img src="/img/armes/shuriken.png" alt="Shuriken" class="left"/>
				The shuriken is also a basic ninja weapon. Who has already seen a true ninja without shuriken? As the other long range weapons, the shuriken undergoes the gravity and then do not reach the far away enemies . The kunai is better than the shuriken on this point, because the shuriken has a smaller range. However you can throw more shurikens at a time, but it's dealing less damages than a kunai. It's up to you to see which one you prefer! As kunais, you can get more shurikens in the weapon boxes.<br/>
				<br/>
				<h4>Shaded Shuriken</h4>
				<img src="/img/armes/ombre.png" alt="Shaded Shuriken" class="left"/>The shuriken of The shadow shuriken is an enormous shuriken which never misses its target! This weapon is as powerful as the sword but with a long range. However, you’ll fin it in very limited quantity. Use it at the right time !<br/>
				<br/>
				<h4>Fumigène</h4>
				<img src="/img/armes/fumigene.png" alt="Fumigene" class="left"/>The smoke bomb isn’t really a weapon since it doesn’t inflict damages. It allows you to run away during a badly engaged battle, or gives you a short break by giving off a large cloud of smoke during a few seconds. Your alias is also hidden in the meantime. It’s up to you to take the best advantage of this “tactical” weapon.<br/>
				<br/>
				<h4>Makibishi</h4>
				<img src="/img/armes/makibishi.png" alt="Makibishi" class="left"/>A makibishi is an assembly of four nails. Sent by handful of six, they allow you to trap the area where they fall. By running after an enemy who has launched his makibishi, you take the risk to stick them into your feet (inducing damages) and to cut your speed by half during a few seconds. Makibishi remain on the map as long as nobody walks on them (or as long as the trapper doesn’t disconnect)]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="Classes"  href="/manuel-ninja/classe.php">
				<contenu><![CDATA[<img src="/img/classes.jpg" alt="classes's opposition" class="right"/>
				As you certainly know (if you have already started to play), the Ninja Tooken adventure begins with the choice of your class. This choice allows you to specialize in an element by unlocking very <a href="/manuel-ninja/jutsu.php#classe" title="jutsus">specifics jutsus</a>.
				<br/>
				<br/>
				Among these five classes you will find :
				<ul>
					<li>Suiton (the water wich has for enemy Doton),</li>
					<li>et Katon (the fire wich has for enemy Suiton),</li>
					<li>Futon (the wind wich has for enemy Katon),</li>
					<li>Raiton (the lightning wich has for enemy Futon),</li>
					<li>Doton (the earth wich has for enemy Raiton).</li>
				</ul>
				<br/>
				<h3>Principle of the oppositions of classes<br/></h3>
				Each classes is dominant on another one. It means that a ninja will deal more damages to an opposite class ninja.<br/>
				For example a Suiton ninja will deal 10% more damage to a Katon ninja. But the ninja Katon will also make that rate of damage to a Futon ninja. Here is a graph illustrating the ascendancies :<br/>
				<br/>
				Do not forget that you can see the percentages of ninja of every class at the homepage bottom. Choose wisely your class according to the classes already present in the game. If there is 50% of Doton ninjas, you’d rather choose Raiton !<br/>
				<br/><br/>
				As said in the introduction, each class have two specific jutsus. These jutsus are probably going to determine your class choice.
				<p align="center"><img src="/img/fresque.jpg" class="center" alt=""/><br/></p>
				<strong>Suiton</strong> : Walk on water, Tsunami<br/>
				<strong>Futon</strong> : Invisibility, Tornado<br/>
				<strong>Katon</strong> : Fire defence, Phoenix<br/>
				<strong>Raiton</strong> : Multishot, Teleportation<br/>
				<strong>Doton</strong> : Metamorphosis, Thorns of rock<br/>
				<br/>
				Go to the <a href="/manuel-ninja/jutsu.php#classe" alt="Jutsus" title="Jutsus">classes jutsus</a> to know more.]]></contenu>
			</partie>
		</partie>
		<partie nom="Options">
			<partie nom="Keys Setting" href="/manuel-ninja/keys-setting.php">
				<contenu><![CDATA[<img src="/img/touches.gif" alt="Keys Setting" class="right"/>
				Indeed, Ninja Tooken is a complete game! But no worries, you can modify absolutely all game controls whenever you want.<br/>
				<br/>
				So, go to the menu "Options", then "Controls". You should see the complete list of the actions with the associated key. And if you have any doubt about an action, you just have to put your mouse on the corresponding text to have an explanation.<br/>
				Then nothing is more simple, click the button corresponding to the key you want to modify and press on the one you’d rather use. But be careful, do not assign the same key to several different actions, because the previous action will not work any more...<br/>
				These modifications are on your computer only, so if you play somewhere else, do not forget to do it a second time!<br/><br/>
				By the way, you will notice that from the same menu you can modify the mouse sensibility: the more it's raised, the more your ninja will turn quickly.]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="Video and Sound settings" href="/manuel-ninja/video-settings.php">
				<contenu><![CDATA[<img src="/img/audioVideo.gif" alt="Video and Sound settings" class="right"/>
				From the menu "Options", then "Audio", you can modify the FX and background music volumes.<br/>
				<br/>
				In the "Graphic" menu you can modify the display quality of the 3D. By default, this one is set as "Simple". If you notice slowings down, you can decrease it, and if you have the very last efficient device, do not hesitate to increase it, you won’t regret it !<br/>
				<br/>
				Please notice that the parameter " automatic selection " is going to choose the most adapted game setting.<br/>
				According to the configuration of your pc, this parameter setting can be badass (returning ceaseless between two graphic quality levels): So don’t hesitate and make tests !]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="System (whazat)" href="/manuel-ninja/system.php">
				<contenu><![CDATA[<img src="/img/systeme.gif" alt="System (whazat)" class="right"/>
				From the "Options" menu, then "System", you can see purely informative informations which detect the version of the plug-in used, as well as your graphic board.<br/>
				<br/>
				These informations are given in an informative way to check that everything corresponds to what you have effectively on your pc, so now hurry up and PLAY !!!]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="Requests of Improvements and bugs" href="/manuel-ninja/improvement-bug.php">
				<contenu><![CDATA[You play for a long time now, and you have noticed bugs, or you have ideas to improve the game ?<br/>
				You just have to send us a message here : <a href="/forum.php?ID=65#forum65" alt="improvement and bug" title="improvement and bug">Forum : improvement and bugs</a>.]]></contenu>
			</partie>
		</partie>
	</partie>
	<partie nom="FAQ" href="/faq.php">
		<partie nom="General questions" href="/faq.php#q1">
			<partie nom="What's Ninja Tooken ?" href="/faq.php#q11">
				<contenu><![CDATA[Ninja Tooken is an online ninja FPS multiplayer game, nay Ninja Tooken is the ONLY one. Inspired by manga, Ninja Tooken suggests you getting into rôle with a ninja, which can evolve according to your desires. Classes, weapons, capacities, you can choose your way. Directly playable in your favourite browser (Firefox, Chrome, Opera, Christopher Colombus, Safari, and even Internet Explorer), Ninja Tooken is totally made in 3D and works with most of the computers (mine is 5 years old and it works perfectly !).]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="Why subscribing ?" href="/faq.php#q12">
				<contenu><![CDATA[You can play without subscribing, but what you've done will not be saved. Please notice that the account of Ninja Tooken is the same than the one of the website n-c-team.com: your avatar, your messaging system, your parameters: everything is set.<br/>
				If you are already registered on the NCT, let Ninja Tooken leads you.]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="Do we have to pay for playing ?" href="/faq.php#q13">
				<contenu><![CDATA[NO, absolutely not! Ninja Tooken is a FREE game, and it is just necessary to register (but that is also free)! We do not obviously accept the donations... To pay the servers of Ninja Tooken, we are using the advertising on the site.<br/>
				- Sure, today it is free, but in a month we will have to pay, it is the Global Financial Crisis, isn't it ?<br/>
				- But I have already said that ! Ninja Tooken is free and will stay free for ever! No worries about this, so stop annoying me !]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="Who are you, and why this game ?" href="/faq.php#q14">
				<contenu><![CDATA[We are a team of passionate persons: students, professionals, or simple newbies !<br/>
				This game allows to express our skills, to develop them, but also and especially to please us.]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="When can we have the next versions ?" href="/faq.php#q15">
				<contenu><![CDATA[Unfortunately the time is what gives out: we work during our spare time without schedule and above all for the pleasure.<br/>
				And as the creation of a video game takes a lot of time, it is impossible to us to give another answer than: " When it's done " !]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="What can I do to help you ?" href="/faq.php#q16">
				<contenu><![CDATA[It's very easy: speak about Ninja Tooken around you! In your MSN nickname, on your site, your blog, facebook, Twitter... Even a small adress! That's it. It is perfect for a partner link, for MSN or facebook. As you like it !]]></contenu>
			</partie>
		</partie>
		<partie nom="Technical problems" href="/faq.php#q2">
			<partie nom="How to change the character name, or to delete my account ?" href="/faq.php#q21">
				<contenu><![CDATA[Once your account was created, you cannot change the character name, it is necessary to delete your account and to recreate the other one !<br/>
				To delete your account, you just have to go to your <a href="#" class="paramDelete">parameters</a> and to click the button "deletion" which is at the bottom of the page. Take care, the deletion is definitive and your character cannot be given back.]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="Why I have a blank page and then nothing ?" href="/faq.php#q22">
				<contenu><![CDATA[First look if you have correctly installed the plugin unity3D available <a href="http://unity3d.com/webplayer/" target="_blank">here</a> (the installation is fast and does not require to reboot the browser).<br/>
				Then verify that you can indeed see the <a href="http://unity3d.com/gallery/live-demos/index.html#tropical-paradise" target="_blank">Unity3d's demo</a>.<br/>
				If yes, goes on <a href="http://www.m2h.nl/files/HWstats.html" target="_blank">this page</a>, then copy and paste the contents in the forum "<a href="/forum.php?ID=65">Improvement and Bug</a>". Try to be precise in the description of your problem, and before posting look if somebody has already had the same problem. We shall can help you,so that you can join us in the game !<br/>
				Otherwise, verify that the drivers of your graphics board are indeed updated, or try to go on the game with another browser !]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="The game is loading then suddenly stop before 100 %, What can I do ?" href="/faq.php#q23">
				<contenu><![CDATA[If the game doesn't load completely, it is because your connection had a sudden network disconnetion during the load. There is currently, no automatic resuming of the download. To resume the load of the game and be able to play correctly, you just have to empty the <a href="http://www.libellules.ch/support/cache.php" target="_blank">cache storage of your browser</a> and <a href="http://webplayer.unity3d.com/setup/" target="_blank">of Unity</a>, and then to refresh the page. Have a lot of fun !]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="Why I do not manage to join a game ?" href="/faq.php#q24">
				<contenu><![CDATA[NinjaTooken uses PhotonNetwork Cloud for multiplayer. There are several scenarios where you may have a problem <br/>
					<ul>
						<li>a firewall may be the case, then you only have to authorize the connection request from Photon </ li>
						<li>anti-virus can also block connections : try to disableit during connection... if you can connect a bit of setup is also required (inquire into the FAQ of your antivirus) </ li>
						<li>the problem may also come from your router or proxy...</ li>
					</ul>
					Access to the control panel of the router. A fast research on Internet on the model of your router should give you the informations for this stage and the following ones.</li>
					Activate the mode DMZ (or " demilitarized zone "). Try to reboot Ninja Tooken, and it should work! If you cannot connect in the other games again, then it is not a problem of router: So it's useless to try the other stages, and go directly to the next part.<br/>
					Desactivate the DMZ mode, then verifies if the mode UPnP (Universal Plug and Play) is activated, to allow the automatic rerouting of the ports. It is indeed necessary to avoid leaving the router without the DMZ mode, because you become a pray with some internet attacks.<br/>
					If the DMZ mode works, but not the UpnP mode, the last solution is to add yourself The rerouting of port <strong>5055</strong> UDP (adding ports 5056 UDP and TCP in 4520/4530/4531/843 can help if the connection does not work best). You can use Port Map if you are on the X operating system.
				</ul>
				<br/>
				]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="Why I do not manage to connect in my account ?" href="/faq.php#q25">
				<contenu><![CDATA[Several problems can prevent you from connecting correctly :
				<ul>
					<li>You have not validated your user account yet: an e-mail must be sent to you containing a link of validation. Click it, and connect!</li>
					<li>If you forgot your password, you just have to click the link at the top of page " forgotten password?", a new password will be sent to you with an e-mail.</li>
					<li>Your nickname or your password contains characters which aren't Latin (you wanted to show off by writing in Japanese?). To correct the problem, <a href="/nous-contacter.php" alt="contact us" title="contact us">contact us</a> !</li>
					<li>The server is overloaded: no miracles, you have to wait !</li>
				</ul>]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="The game is lagging, what can I do ?" href="/faq.php#q26">
				<contenu><![CDATA[The game can slow down to you but not for the other players (who will see you moving in a hatched way). It is generally due to a problem of <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ping" target="_blank">ping</a> (too high).<br/>
				To verify your ping, you can go at : <a href="http://ping.eu/ping/" target="_blank">http://ping.eu/ping/</a> and type in the url of the PhotonCloud Service : app.exitgamescloud.com<br/>
				A correct ping is on average below 20ms. If yours is above, contact your Internet Service Provider.<br/>
				Notice that the ping has no relation with your speed of download, which can be the second problem of lagging: Be sure that you download nothing when you play !]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="The game is lagging at my place, what can I do ?" href="/faq.php#q27">
				<contenu><![CDATA[If the game is slowing down, you can decrease the graphic quality of the game in the menu: "options" then "graphs".<br/>
				More information is available in <a href="/manuel-ninja/parametrage-video.php" title="Paramétrage de la vidéo et du son">the textbook of the ninja: " parameter setting of the video and the sound "</a>.<br/>
				You can also reduce the resolution to improve system performance in "full screen".]]></contenu>
			</partie>
			<partie nom="When i'm playing, the mouse does not answer any more, what can I do ?" href="/faq.php#q28">
				<contenu><![CDATA[There is for the current version of Unity3D (a graphic engine used for NinjaTooken) a bug preventing the mouse from working correctly with the Internet Explorer browser. This bug can occur but not necessarily always.<br/>
				If it's happening, you can switch your browser to an another one.]]></contenu>
			</partie>
		</partie>
	</partie>
	<reglement><![CDATA[<h1>Regulation</h1>
		By joining Ninja Tooken, you engaged yourself to respect a few rules. These ones were created in order to keep a good atmosphere during the game. Any player who is violating those rules exposes himself to the banishment of his account without noticing. Here’s a non exhaustive list of rules to be respected:<br/><br/>
		<h2>Account and alias</h2>
		Your ninja’s alias must respect the following rules :
		<ul>
			<li>No coarseness, no insults</li>
			<li>No sexual or pornographic connotation</li>
			<li>No references to politics, ethnic groups, communities or religions.</li>
			<li>No registered trademarks</li>
			<li>No references to illegal products</li>
			<li>No admin or moderator look like aliases</li>
		</ul>
		It is forbidden to lend ones account, because of the various possible abuses (faster EXP earning, etc…)<br/><br/>
		In case of violation of this last rule, both players incur sanctions.<br/><br/>
		<h2>Chat/Forum/Clans</h2>
		<ul>
			<li>Flood, (several repetition of the same message in a short time) isn’t allowed.</li>
			<li>It is forbidden to advertise for another website, including those related to Ninja Tooken.</li>
			<li>Insulting, pornographic, religious, xenophobic, homophobic, political, illegal product positive presentation and consumption inciting, or even just Justin Bieber talk about speeches are strictly forbidden.</li>
			<li>Please respect grammar! And everyone will be more than happy.</li>
		</ul>
		<h2>Game respect</h2>
		<ul>
			<li>Usurping someone’s identity is forbidden, no matters which one it is (simple player, moderator, admin) or the reason (right or wrong).</li>
			<li>Disclosing private and/or personal content about other players is prohibited.</li>
			<li>From a general point of view, it is forbidden to harm the good progression of the game.</li>
		</ul>
		<h2>Business</h2>
		The following actions are forbidden:
		<ul>
			<li>Trading or exchanging accounts or clans</li>
			<li>Organizing paying competitions, animations or tournaments.</li>
		</ul>
		<h2>Cheating</h2>
		<ul>
			<li>Misuse of a game bug is forbidden. Every anomaly is to be reported using the forum’s Bug & Improvement section, or using the contact form.</li>
			<li>Using a third program in order to corrupt the game is forbidden.</li>
			<li>You are allowed to own several accounts.</li>
			<li>It is forbidden to play with more than one account in the same game.</li>
	</ul>]]></reglement>
	<team><![CDATA[<h2>Ninja Tooken, c'est des ninjas et des shurikens, mais c'est aussi...</h2>

	<h3>Infographie 3D</h3>

	<h4>Andre Doan aka Drey77</h4>
	Artiste 3D en recherche d'emploi (animation, modélisation, et textures)<br/>
	Mail : <a href="mailto:%61%6E%64%72%65%2E%64%6F%61%6E%40%67%6D%61%69%6C%2E%63%6F%6D">andre.doan -at- gmail.com</a><br/>
	Site : <a target="_blank" href="http://www.andredoan.com/">http://www.andredoan.com/</a><br/>
	<br/>

	<h4>Régis Roussot aka Chaukopeps</h4>
	Infographiste, Animateur 3D (animation, modélisation, et textures)<br/>
	Mail : <a href="mailto:%72%65%67%69%73%72%6F%75%73%73%6F%74%40%68%6F%74%6D%61%69%6C%2E%66%72">regisroussot -at- hotmail.fr</a><br/>
	Site : <a target="_blank" href="http://chaukopeps.over-blog.fr/">http://chaukopeps.over-blog.fr/</a><br/>
	<br/>

	<h4>Jonathan Persoons</h4>
	Étudiant (modélisation, et textures)<br/>
	Mail : <a href="mailto:%70%65%72%73%6F%6F%6E%73%6A%40%67%6D%61%69%6C%2E%63%6F%6D">persoonsj -at- gmail.com</a><br/>
	Facebook : <a target="_blank" href="http://www.facebook.com/profile.php?ref=profile&amp;id=854619641">http://www.facebook.com/profile.php?ref=profile&amp;id=854619641</a><br/>
	<br/>

	<h4>Antoine Heckmann aka MrSlher</h4>
	Étudiant en animation 3D/Jeux video (modélisation, et textures)<br/>
	Mail : <a href="mailto:%6E%65%67%72%6F%5F%64%6F%6E%6E%40%68%6F%74%6D%61%69%6C%2E%63%6F%6D">negro_donn -at- hotmail.com</a><br/>
	<br/>

	<h4>Manakel</h4>
	Modélisation, et textures<br/>

	<h4>Yadoob</h4>
	Modélisation, et textures<br/>
	Blog : <a href="http://utopies.over-blog.fr/" title="http://utopies.over-blog.fr/">http://utopies.over-blog.fr/</a><br/>

	<h4>Kay</h4>
	Modélisation et textures<br/>
	<br/>

	<h4>Everest</h4>
	Modélisation et textures<br/>
	<br/>
	
	<h3>Infographie 2D</h3>

	<h4>Eberhard</h4>
	Character design, et Interface 2D<br/>
	<br/>

	<h4>Anomen</h4>
	Illustrations, textures, et Webdesign<br/>
	<br/>

	<h3>Contenus et gestion</h3>

	<h4>Neo[F]abien-Sama</h4>
	<br/>


	<h3>Sound Design</h3>

	<h4>Will Alexander</h4>
	SoundCloud : <a href="https://soundcloud.com/willalexander" title="https://soundcloud.com/willalexander">https://soundcloud.com/willalexander</a><br/>

	<h4>Crystalmir</h4>
	<br/>

	<h3>Bêta-testing</h3>

	<h4>Yondame-Hokage</h4>
	<br/>

	<h4>Poups229</h4>
	Étudiant<br/>
	<br/>

	<h3>Administration réseau</h3>

	<h4>G-Rom</h4>
	<h4>Wanix</h4>
	<br/>

	<h3>Animation de la communauté</h3>

	<h4>Casey</h4>
	Modération site<br/>
	<h4>Soxsoxsox</h4>
	Modération site<br/>
	Mail : <a href="mailto:%74%68%6F%6D%61%73%33%30%33%40%68%6F%74%6D%61%69%6C%2E%66%72">thomas303 -at- hotmail.fr</a><br/>
	Facebook : <a target="_blank" href="http://fr-fr.facebook.com/people/Soxsoxsox-Threesox/100002183121158">http://fr-fr.facebook.com/people/Soxsoxsox-Threesox/100002183121158</a><br/>
	<br/>
	<h4>Yondame-Hokage</h4>
	Modération site<br/>
	Mail : <a href="mailto:%44%79%6C%61%6E%33%32%35%30%40%68%6F%74%6D%61%69%6C%2E%63%6F%6D">Dylan3250 -at- hotmail.com</a><br/>
	Facebook : <a target="_blank" href="http://fr-fr.facebook.com/people/Shinz%C3%B4-Takez%C3%B4/100002317862191">http://fr-fr.facebook.com/people/Shinz%C3%B4-Takez%C3%B4/100002317862191</a><br/>
	<br/>
	<h4>Yusei32</h4>
	Organisation évènementielle<br/>
	<h4>Rydax</h4>
	Modération Chat<br/>
	<br/>

	<h3>Traduction</h3>

	<h4>Casey</h4>
	Traduction - Son<br/>
	Mail : <a href="mailto:%68%6F%70%65%6C%65%73%73%75%74%6F%70%69%61%6E%40%67%6D%61%69%6C%2E%63%6F%6D">hopelessutopian -at- gmail.com</a>
	<br/>
	<h4>Soxsoxsox</h4>
	Modération site<br/>
	Mail : <a href="mailto:%74%68%6F%6D%61%73%33%30%33%40%68%6F%74%6D%61%69%6C%2E%66%72">thomas303 -at- hotmail.fr</a><br/>
	Facebook : <a target="_blank" href="http://fr-fr.facebook.com/people/Soxsoxsox-Threesox/100002183121158">http://fr-fr.facebook.com/people/Soxsoxsox-Threesox/100002183121158</a><br/>
	<br/>


	<h3>Programmation et intégration</h3>

	<h4>2Kin</h4>
	<br/>
	<br/>
	Pour toutes questions, n'hésitez pas à <a target="_blank" href="/nous-contacter.php" alt="nous contacter" title="nous contacter">nous contacter</a> !
	<br/>]]></team>
	<mention><![CDATA[<strong>BUSINESS PRIVACY POLICY</strong><br>
	This privacy policy sets out how Ninja Tooken uses and protects any information that you give Ninja Tooken when you use this website.<br/>
	Ninja Tooken is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.<br/>
	Ninja Tooken may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 26th June 2011.<br/>
	<br/>
	<strong>WHAT WE COLLECT</strong><br/>
	We may collect the following information:<br/>
	· name and job title<br/>
	· contact information including email address<br/>
	· demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests<br/>
	· other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers<br/>
	<br/>
	<strong>WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER</strong><br/>
	We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:<br/>
	· Internal record keeping.<br/>
	· We may use the information to improve our products and services.<br/>
	· We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.<br/>
	· From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.<br/>
	<br/>
	<strong>SECURITY</strong><br/>
	We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.<br/>
	<br/>
	<strong>HOW WE USE COOKIES</strong><br/>
	A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.<br/>
	We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.<br/>
	Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.<br/>
	You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.<br/>
	<br/>
	<strong>LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES</strong><br/>
	Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.<br/>
	<br/>
	<strong>CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION</strong><br/>
	You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:<br/>
	· whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes<br/>
	· if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us by using the contact form<br/>
	We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.<br/>
	You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable.<br/>
	If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.]]></mention>
	<reglementModeration><![CDATA[
	In order to ensure a fun and safe game experience to all NinjaTooken players, the team set up the “Abuse Moderation” section, whereby every user is empowered to lay down what behaviour is considered acceptable, and to punish those considered as inacceptable.<br/>
	Here is how you, as a user, might be reported, how works the evaluation of those reports, and the possible punishment. This Policy is applied jointly with the game rules.<br/>
	<br/>
	<strong>HOW TO SUBMIT A REPORT?</strong><br/>
	During an on-line game, each user can create a report against any other user connected to the same game, using the “Social” section from the in-game menu (“m” key by default), and then by clicking on “Report an abuse”, at the right under the name of the incriminated user.<br/>
	You can create a report against any player who, according to you, didn’t respect the game rules or acted in an immoral way.<br/>
	During one game, if at least half the players report the same user, then this one will be automatically disconnected from this game and won’t be able to join it again.<br/>
	<br/>
	<strong>WHAT EVIDENCES ARE PROVIDED TO “JUDGE” A CASE ?</strong><br/>
	When a user has been reported in a game, an “Abuse Moderation” case file is automatically created, associated to a text report containing the following informations:<br/>
	<ul>
		<li>the reported user’s ninja alias</li>
		<li>the reported user’s ninja statistics</li>
		<li>the full chat history of the game during which the user has been reported</li>
	</ul>
	One doesn’t vote for each individual text report: he has a unique vote concerning the whole case file. Therefore, reading all text reports helps a user to get the knowledge of misconducts and context, allowing him to be precise and fair in his vote for or against disciplinary sanctions.<br/>
	<br/>
	<strong>HOW DOES THE VOTE TAKE PLACE ?</strong><br/>
	Once one has examined the reports, he can give it a mark from 1 to 5 shuriken, respectively in order to “acquit” or “punish”:<br/>
	<ul>
		<li>1 shuriken: Acquit!</li>
		<li>2 shurikens: Punish! By decreasing the amount of experience earned by 20%</li>
		<li>3 shurikens: Punish! By decreasing the amount of experience earned by 40%</li>
		<li>4 shurikens: Punish! By decreasing the amount of experience earned by 60%</li>
		<li>5 shurikens: Punish! By decreasing the amount of experience earned by 80%</li>
	</ul>
	If a player gets a 80% penalty on his EXP, then, instead of 100 points for example, he will only get 20 points.<br/>
	The penalty is applied from 10 votes.<br/>

	Moderators and administrators of NinjaTooken are able to acquit the incriminated user by deleting reports and votes, or to banish him from the game if necessary.<br/>
	You’ll be warned every time a user creates a report against you, but you won’t be kept noticed of the evolution of the file. For that, you’ll have to check regularly the “Abuse Moderation” section.<br/>
	<br/>
	<strong>ELIGIBILITY AND PARTICIPATION / WHO CAN VOTE ?</strong><br/>
	Only users who have reached the level 55 can vote. Those who are eligible and wish to participate must log in the NinjaTooken website, and read and agree to this Policy. 
	]]></reglementModeration>
	<texte>
		<txt><![CDATA[My page :]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Shinobi Clan :]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Clan ##DROIT##, member since ##DATE##]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Edit]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[There is no message yet.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Show more messages]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Go to page :]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Post a message]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Title]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Contain]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Post]]></txt><!--10-->
		<txt><![CDATA[This clan has been created the ##DATE##, and groups ##NUM## ninja(s) together for an average level of ##LEVEL##.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Clan]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Clan list]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Classify :]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[By date]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[By shinobi number]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[By shinobi average level]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Show more clans]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Add a clan]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Clan name]]></txt><!--20-->
		<txt><![CDATA[Clan website]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Clan story]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Clan Kamon (<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kamon_%28crest%29" target="_blank">Kamon</a>)]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Add]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[I don't want automatic newsletter anymore]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Invalid e-mail]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Automatic messages have been cancelled.:]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[If you want to unsubscribe from the automatic newsletter,please fill the text field :]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Email adress]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[I accept that you send me newsletters (1 time per month max)]]></txt><!--30-->
		<txt><![CDATA[I wish to be warned by e-mail of the arriving of new messages in my private mailbox.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The NCT has computing means to manage information exchanges between members.<br/>
		The registered informations are reserved to the NCT staff, and only the nickname, gender and birthdate are communicated.<br/>
		According to articles 39 and following of the law N 78-17 of January 6th, 1978 [France] relative to the computing, files and liberty, every person can obtain communication and, if necessary, rectification or deletion of the informations concerning him(her) <a href="/nous-contacter.php"> by sending this request with the button "contact us"</a> or <a href="#" class="paramGeneral"> her settings pannel.</a>.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Send]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Erase]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Field with * are compulsory.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA["Ninja Tooken" Team]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Friends]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Rules]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Legal Notices]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Contact us]]></txt><!--40-->
		<txt><![CDATA[Subscribe]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Connect]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Close]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[To save your level and your ninja, you have to create an account !]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Nickname]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Password]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Repeat]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[E-mail]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Name]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[First Name]]></txt><!--50-->
		<txt><![CDATA[Town]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Telephone]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Gender]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Male]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Female]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Birthdate]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[January]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[February]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[March]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[April]]></txt><!--60-->
		<txt><![CDATA[May]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[June]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[July]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[August]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[September]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[October]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[November]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Decembrer]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Language]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Description]]></txt><!--70-->
		<txt><![CDATA[Connection with Facebook]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Connection]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Password forgotten?]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Games list]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Forum]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Last message]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[New topic]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Show more messages]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Last registered user]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[##NUM1## registered users and ##NUM2## messages written.]]></txt><!--80-->
		<txt><![CDATA[last]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[No message in this forum yet.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[No answer to this message yet.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Ninja's Guide]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[answer(s)]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Edit]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[delete this message?]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[yes]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[no]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[delete]]></txt><!--90-->
		<txt><![CDATA[answer]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Quote]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Subscribe to NinjaTooken !]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Subscribing with Facebook]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[connect with Facebook]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Basic Inscription]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[+ Inform the optional information !]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[incorrect login]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[incorrect email adress]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[the password is not the same]]></txt><!--100-->
		<txt><![CDATA[The password must be 6 letters long or more.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Website subscribing has been cancelled. :]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Deleted]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[message(s)]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Written the]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[This ninja is from the clan]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Share]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Community]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[FAQ]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Inscription]]></txt><!--110-->
		<txt><![CDATA[Create your ninja]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Your friends]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You cancelled the edition of your personnal informations.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Edit my personnal informations.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Incorrect email adress]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Your message does not have a title.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Your message is not written.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Message sending cancelled.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Your email adress]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Topic]]></txt><!--120-->
		<txt><![CDATA[User datasheet]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Signature (big one)]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Html code for this signature :]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[BBCode for this signature :]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Html Code for this avatar:]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[BBCode for this avatar :]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Insert this image in a forum]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Insert this image in a blog]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Signature (tiny one)]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Avatar]]></txt><!--130-->
		<txt><![CDATA[Send a message to ##PSEUDO##]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Man]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Woman]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Born the ##DATE##]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Happy Birthday!]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[(##AGE## years old)]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Is here since ##DATE##]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Activated the ##DATE##]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Not activated yet.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Member of...]]></txt><!--140-->
		<txt><![CDATA[ As ]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[His last messages]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[##PSEUDO## has written a message]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Last update since ##DATE##]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Search an user]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You haven't written any user to search.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Searching cancelled :]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Research results: '##LOGIN##']]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[No results found for '##RECHERCHE##']]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Ninja Account validation]]></txt><!--150-->
		<txt><![CDATA[You have subscribed to Ninja Tooken. To end your inscription, and connect to the game, <a href="http://www.ninjatooken.com/?c=##CODE##" target="_blank">click here</a> (or copy/paste this adress in your navigator: http://www.ninjatooken.com/?c=##CODE##).]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Your inscription has been well received..<br/> A mail has been sent with a link that allows you to finalize your inscription.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The mail that allows you to activate your account could not have been sent. To finalize your inscription, <a href="http://www.ninjatooken.com/?c=##CODE##">click here</a>.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Our server is buzy, try again later...]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Invalid password]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[This login is already used !]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[This email adress is already used!]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Invalid email adress.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[This part is only readable with a private access. Please contact us.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[New private message from ##LOGIN##]]></txt><!--160-->
		<txt><![CDATA[You have a new private message from ##LOGIN##.<br/>You have to be connected on the website to read it!]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[An issue occurred while sending the message.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[One of the message addressee couldn't be found]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Message(s) properly deleted]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Failure while deleting.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Archiving properly done.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Failure while archiving.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Message sent to ##LISTE##]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Addressee couldn't be found, sending cancelled...<br/>Fields necessary to send the message aren't properly filled, sending cancelled...]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Send a message :]]></txt><!--170-->
		<txt><![CDATA[Addressee]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Archive]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[New message]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Inbox]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Sendings]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Archives]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Delete selection]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Select all]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Archive selection]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[from]]></txt><!--180-->
		<txt><![CDATA[to]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[No messages for the moment...]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[My informations]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[My password]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Delete my account]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Modifications saved]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Modify the image]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[See the current avatar]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Account deleted.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Warning : deleting a account is final, informations about your ninja will be definitively lost.]]></txt><!--190-->
		<txt><![CDATA[The new password is correctly saved.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The current password is false.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The new password isn't correctly repeted.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[At least one field isn't fill]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Old one]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[New one]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Reapeat the new one]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Connexion via Facebook]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Welcome to NinjaTooken ##LOGIN## !<br/><br/>You've just connected your Facebook account to play NinjaTooken.<br/>Don't forget to update your <a href='/parametres.php' title='Mes paramètres'>infos NinjaTooken</a> to improve the game experience (avatar, signature, email...).<br/><br/>See you soon ingame ;)<br/>The NinjaTooken team]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Messaging]]></txt><!--200-->
		<txt><![CDATA[Parameters]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Log out]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[##NUM## unread message(s)]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Recall your connection parameters]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You asked for your connection parameters on the NCT website.<br/> If it's not the case, do not hesitate to contact an admin...]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Warning, you haven't activated your account yet, to do so, <a href="##ACTIVATION##" target="_blank">Click here</a>]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Your account has been shut down by a moderator...]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The clan has been correctly added.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Our server is tired, try again to add your clan later..]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[This clan name is already used. Choose another one!]]></txt><!--210-->
		<txt><![CDATA[You're already a part of a clan. You can't create a new one.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The clan name and/or description fields aren't fill. Adding cancelled.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You must be connected to join a clan.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[New message from ##LOGIN##]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You've just received a private message from ##LOGIN##.<br/> Connect on the website to read it!]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[This clan has been wiped out of history]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You've just quitted this clan.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You've just applied in this clan as a "warrior"]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You're already a part of this clan.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You've been banned from this clan or you're waiting for a recruitment.]]></txt><!--220-->
		<txt><![CDATA[The shinobi has been promoted to the rank of "intendant".]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The shinobi has been degraded to the rank of "warrior".]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Rank modification]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Your rank within the clan has been modified.<br/><a href="##URL##">Page du clan</a>]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The shinobi has been banned]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The shinobi has been recruited.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Banishment]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You've been banned from the clan.<br/><a href="##URL##">Page du clan</a>]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Recruit]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Your application hold our attention, and we annouce you with great pleasure that you're now a member of the clan!<br/>Congratulations !<br/><a href="##URL##">Clan page</a>]]></txt><!--230-->
		<txt><![CDATA[The shinobi hasn't been accepted.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[However it was interesting, your application has not been accepted. Keep on progressing and maybe we'll see you soon in the clan!<br/><a href="##URL##">Clan page</a>]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Quit this clan]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Cancel myapplication]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Accepted]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Applicant]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Promote as "Intendant"]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Can banish clan shinobis, except the clan master]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Degrade as "Warrior"]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[No particular rights]]></txt><!--240-->
		<txt><![CDATA[Banish this shinobi]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Accept this shinobi]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Refuse this shinobi]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Join this clan]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[This clan doesn't exist anymore]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The art of manipulating the fire]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The art of manipulating the water]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The art of manipulating the earth]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The art of manipulating the lightning]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The art of manipulating the wind]]></txt><!--250-->
		<txt><![CDATA[Your registration is completed, you can now connect to the website .]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Your registration couldn't be completed, our server suffered from our success ... re-tried later.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You are already activated. If you forgot your password, click on forgotten password .]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[This activation code is a crock. Copy and paste the URL provided in your mail in order to finalize your registration .]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You have just activate your NinjaTooken account.<br/>You can now log on and be embark on the adventure!]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Subscribtion to NinjaTooken]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Missions completed...]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Jutsu(s) controled...]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[on]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Slug]]></txt><!--260-->
		<txt><![CDATA[Follower]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Messenger]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Sprinter]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Apprentice]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Executioner]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Assassin]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Executor]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Race]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Murder]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You are already logged in, you can already <a href="/jouer.php#jouer" title='jouer'>play at NinjaTooken</a> without having to create another account (see <a href='#' class='paramGeneral' title='my settings'>parameters</a> from my account).<br/>A Ninja is available for each account created.]]></txt><!--270-->
		<txt><![CDATA[Delete from my friend's list]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[This mail is not used. If you have forgotten your connection settings <br/> or you have not received your activation mail, <a href="javascript:popMdpOublie();" title="forgotten password?"> click here </a>.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Your profile was successfully updated.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Are you sure you want to delete your account ?]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[My friends]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Add a friend]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Add]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[##PSEUDO## has correctly been added to your friend's list]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Problem when adding your friend]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[New Friend !]]></txt><!--280-->
		<txt><![CDATA[##PSEUDO## has noticed your awesomeness and has decided to bring you into his friend's list.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Problem when deleting this friend]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[One fewer friend...]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[##PSEUDO## no longer consider you the same way in the early days and decided not to continue your relationship.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[added on...]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You have not added friend yet.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The ninja has correctly been deleted from your friend's list.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Ingame ?]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[In the chatroom ?]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Verbale abuse]]></txt><!--290-->
		<txt><![CDATA[Verbal abuse were reported by ##LOGIN##. A report has been submitted to the community that will judge them.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Acquit or punish ?]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[malus of xp]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[votes cast]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The penalty is taken into account after 10 votes.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Abuses found]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Abuse moderation]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Open conversation]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Found by]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[during the game]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[No abuse found yet!]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You do not belong or has applied in any clan.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You're part of this clan :]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You have applied in this clan :]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Rules of moderation abuse]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[User(s) banned after being reported :]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Screenshots]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[No available screenshots.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Image deleted.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Are you sure you want to delete this image ?]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Unknown]]></txt><!--311-->
	</texte>
	<javascript>
		<txt><![CDATA[No results found]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You haven't entered a name for your clan]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You haven't entered a description for your clan]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Clan addition cancelled :]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[An error occured while adding the clan...]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You haven't write your message, so there's nothing to post :p]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You haven't write the subject's title, sending cancelled.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You forgot to enter your login]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You forgot to enter your password]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Connection cancelled :]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Close the window]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Close]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Failure while sending new connection parameters. Try again later.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Wrong e-mail address. Sending cancelled.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The e-mail address you entered isn't linked to any account.<a href="/inscription.php">Subscribe!</a>]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The mail couldn't be sent. Try again later!]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Your new connection parameters have been sent.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Invalid alias and/or password.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You haven't entered your alias and/or your password]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[See my ninja]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Select a message at least !!]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You haven't entered the recipient's name]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You haven't entered the subject of your message]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[You haven't write your message]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Failure during the update, mistake during the sending of datas]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The message can't be sent:]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Failure during the update, mistake during the sending of datas]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Forgot your connection parameters?<br/>Enter your E-mail address to receive them]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[E-mail address]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Invalid e-mail address, sending is impossible.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Return to the form]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Failure during subscription, mistake during the sending of datas]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Your alias isn't correctly entered.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Your password must be at least 8 caracters long.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The repeted password is false.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Invalid e-mail address.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Private page]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Edit]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Cancel]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Deletion of a message is permanent.<br/>Are you sure you want to delete your message nevertheless?]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[There's no text to quote]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[No]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Yes]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Delete]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Loading content...]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Vote not taken into account.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Bad parameters entered.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The level required for voting is 55.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[Problems in determining the uniqueness of the vote.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The voter may not be the person charged.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[The vote has already been done.]]></txt>
		<txt><![CDATA[An error was detected.]]></txt>
	</javascript>
</root>